[2 years later]
Stay away from this stuff
after you get out.
Live a good life.
Go.
Welcome home.
You asked me to keep this for you.
Now it's returned to its rightful owner.
Congratulations on your new life.
These 2 rings
were meant to belong to you.
Hello, Boss.
This place
is the deepest night of this city
and its most complicated corner.
But from now on,
this place will be different.
It is a place
where people who walk in
can forget their troubles.
A place for peace.
And I want to give it to you.
I have always been a pessimist.
[Dearest Episode 24]
If one day I get sick
or have an accident,
it can take my place
to back you up,
be your confidence,
and be your stepping stone.
Ms. Wen.
How have you been?
Envoy Yin.
Nope.
I should call you Commander Yin now.
I'm here to congratulate you.
You really saved Wen Group
all by yourself.
My mother traded her life for it.
I must protect it.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
I've been specially assigned
to be stationed in Nansha.
I won't have many chances
to return to Xinggang.
It's nice to meet you, Wen Jianan.
Well,
I hope to see you again.
Remember to find me next time
you come back.
Not as a special envoy or commander,
nor as an ally or partner,
but
as a friend.
The sun is out.
You tied your hair up.
What's wrong?
Does it look bad?
You look better than
any time I've seen you before.
Ms. Wen.
You've been working for so long,
staring at a cold computer.
Shouldn't you
take a break?
Men really are stumbling blocks on
a woman's path to success.
No matter how important work is,
your health is also important.
Just a little.
Just a little more.
You said the same thing 2 hours ago.
But if this project loses money,
you have to compensate me for everything.
♪ In the darkness
where there is no light ♪
Why do you keep looking at me? Don't look.
♪ At the end of every lonely night ♪
Didn't you say it at the nursing home?
In TV dramas,
that's how they do it.
♪ Now my heart is beating once again ♪
Taking off glasses means a kiss.
♪ Finally I'm breathing past the pain ♪
♪ In the winter breeze,
I feel your breath ♪
♪ Waking up my soul from frozen death ♪
Jiang Yu, let's have a wedding.
♪ Like a miracle, you came in view ♪
Just the two of us.
♪ At the edge of this breaking world ♪
♪ You are the only one
who brought the light ♪
♪ Because it's you ♪
♪ All my sorrows ♪
♪ Fading out of sight ♪
♪ In your arms, I'm born again and new ♪
♪ Holding tightly to my hands and scars ♪
♪ Your deep breathing ♪
Getting married!
♪ Guided like the stars ♪
Ms. Wen Jianan.
Mr. Jiang Yu.
Do you take Mr. Jiang Yu
to be your husband?
♪ Now I'll never let you go ♪
Do you take Ms. Wen Jianan
to be your wife?
♪ At the edge of this breaking world ♪
In sickness and in health.
For richer, for poorer.
♪ You are the only one
who brought the light ♪
For better, for worse.
To love, cherish, and spoil her.
♪ Because it's you ♪
To cherish and love him.
Buy her bags and houses.
♪ All my sorrows ♪
♪ Fading out of sight ♪
Until death do you part?
I do.
♪ In your arms, I'm born again and new ♪
♪ All the cruel darkness fades away ♪
♪ And you bring the colors of the day ♪
♪ I will stay by your side ever-more ♪
♪ The only one who brought me through ♪
♪ Because it's you ♪
Mr. Jiang Yu,
do you take Ms. Wen Jianan
to be your wife?
For richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
for better, for worse,
will you love and cherish her forever,
until death do you part?
I do.
Ms. Wen Jianan,
do you take
Mr. Jiang Yu to be your husband?
For better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
will you love and cherish him,
until death do you part?
I do.
Wen Jianan.
From now on,
I am all yours.
We've come a long way to get here.
No one cherishes this more than I do.
I promise.
No more evil
will tear us apart.
We will never be apart again.
♪ In the darkness
where there is no light ♪
♪ At the end of every lonely night ♪
♪ Now my heart is beating once again ♪
♪ Finally I'm breathing past the pain ♪
♪ In the winter breeze,
I feel your breath ♪
♪ Waking up my soul from frozen death ♪
♪ Like a miracle, you came in view ♪
♪ At the edge of this breaking world ♪
♪ You are the only one
who brought the light ♪
♪ Because it's you ♪
♪ All my sorrows ♪
♪ Fading out of sight ♪